el-nation.com 2013-12-26

# Privacy policy - El Nation

**Effective: March 1, 2013**

This Privacy Policy describes El Nation’s policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. El Nation receives your information through our various web sites, APIs, applications, services and third-parties ("Services"). When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of the country you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by El Nation in any country where El Nation operates.

**Post, Following, Lists and other Public Information:**

Our Services are primarily designed to help you share some information with the world. Our aim is to make the information you provide public. 

**Third Party Services:**

El Nation uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request. 

**Service Providers:**

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy. 

**Modifying Your Personal Information**

If you are a registered user of our Services, you’ll be able to modify the personal information provided and associated with your account.

**Changes to this Policy**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. By continuing to use the Services after some effective changes, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

El Nation Team.
